const questions = [
    {
        question: "What does a yellow traffic light indicate?",
        options: ["Stop", "Proceed with caution", "Speed up", "Go back"],
        correctAnswer: "Proceed with caution",
    },
    {
        question: "What does a red octagonal sign mean?",
        options: ["Stop", "Yield", "Go", "Merge"],
        correctAnswer: "Stop",
    },
    {
        question: "What is the purpose of road signs with a blue background?",
        options: [
            "Danger or caution",
            "Regulatory information",
            "Tourist information",
            "Construction zone",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Regulatory information",
    },
    {
        question:
            "What does a white diamond-shaped sign with an orange symbol indicate?",
        options: [
            "Road work ahead",
            "Stop ahead",
            "Yield ahead",
            "Railroad crossing ahead",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Road work ahead",
    },
    {
        question: "When should you use your turn signals?",
        options: [
            "Only when turning left",
            "Only when turning right",
            "When changing lanes",
            "All of the above",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "All of the above",
    },
    {
        question: "What does a green traffic light indicate?",
        options: ["Stop", "Proceed with caution", "Go", "Slow down"],
        correctAnswer: "Go",
    },
    {
        question:
            "What is the safe following distance in ideal driving conditions?",
        options: ["1 second", "2 seconds", "3 seconds", "4 seconds"],
        correctAnswer: "3 seconds",
    },
    {
        question: "What does a yield sign mean?",
        options: [
            "Stop and wait for traffic to clear",
            "Merge with oncoming traffic",
            "Slow down and be prepared to stop",
            "Proceed without stopping",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Slow down and be prepared to stop",
    },
    {
        question: "What does a double yellow line on the road indicate?",
        options: [
            "No passing allowed",
            "Passing allowed with caution",
            "Passing allowed in both directions",
            "Passing allowed only on the right",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "No passing allowed",
    },
    {
        question: "What should you do if your vehicle starts to skid?",
        options: [
            "Accelerate",
            "Brake hard",
            "Steer in the direction you want to go",
            "Close your eyes",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Steer in the direction you want to go",
    },
];

export default questions;